Guide to the Yale Athletics Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Pictures of Yale athletics, circa 1850-2000; Series I
  - Photographs
    - Football [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1945, football Program (Box 17, Folder 142)
      - 1945,, intramural? (Box 17, Folder 143)
      - 1946 (Box 17, Folder 144)
      - 1947 (Box 17, Folder 144)
      - 1948 (Box 17, Folder 144)
      - 1948, intramural (Box 17, Folder 145)
      - 1949 (Box 17, Folder 145)
      - 1950 (Box 17, Folder 145)
      - 1951 (Box 17, Folder 146)
      - 1952 (Box 17, Folder 146)
      - 1953 (Box 17, Folder 146)
      - 1953, freshman (Box 17, Folder 146)
      - 1954 (Box 17, Folder 147)
      - 1954 Behind the Scenes (Box 17, Folder 147)
      - 1954, intramural (Box 17, Folder 148)
      - 1955 (Box 17, Folder 148)
      - 1956 (Box 17, Folder 149)
      - 1957 (Box 17, Folder 150)
      - 1958 (Box 17, Folder 150)
      - circa 1958 (Box 17, Folder 150)
      - 1959 (Box 17, Folder 151)
      - 1960 (Box 17, Folder 151)
      - circa 1960, action (Box 17, Folder 151)
      - 1961 (Box 17, Folder 152)
      - 1962 (Box 17, Folder 152)
      - 1963 (Box 17, Folder 152)
      - 1964 (Box 17, Folder 153)
      - 1965 Coach Carmen Cozza (Box 17, Folder 153)
      - 1966 (Box 17, Folder 153)
      - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 154)
      - 1967 (Box 18, Folder 154)
      - 1967 (Box 18, Folder 155)
      - 1968 Harvard Stadium Scenes (Box 18, Folder 156)
      - 1969 (Box 18, Folder 156)
      - Keith Bassi, circa 1976 (Box 40, Folder 273)
      - John Rogan, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 274)
      - Kevin Czinger, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 275)
      - Yale-Princeton game, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 276)
      - 1979 Article on Long-time Yale fan (Box 18, Folder 157)
      - Football Y Association Meetings (Box 18, Folder 158)
      - Drawings (Including Drawings by F. Remington) (Box 18, Folder 158)
      - Memorabilia- Press Admit (Box 18, Folder 158)
      - Short Articles on History of Yale football (Box 18, Folder 159)
      - Miscellaneous: Group of graduate Celebrities (Box 18, Folder 159)
      - Description of Yale football film (Box 18, Folder 159)
      - Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 160)
      - Team Portraits (Box 18, Folder 160)
      - Captains (Box 18, Folder 160)
      - Coaches and Trainers (Box 18, Folder 160)
      - Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 161)
      - Practice (Box 18, Folder 161)
      - Action, 2000, no date (Box 18, Folder 161)
      - Unidentified (Box 18, Folder 162)
      - Action (Box 18, Folder 162)
      - Snapshots (Box 18, Folder 162)
      - Spectators (Box 18, Folder 162)
      - Non-Yale (Box 19, Folder 163-64)
    - Frisbee
      - 1970 (Box 31, Folder 264)
      - 1970, action (Box 31, Folder 264)
    - Golf
      - 1904, action (Box 25, Folder 219)
      - 1907-1909 (Box 25, Folder 219)
      - 1924-1927 (Box 25, Folder 219)
      - 1929 (Box 25, Folder 219)
      - 1931-1934 (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - 1936 (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - 1953, action (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - 1962 (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - Unidentified: (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - Team Portraits (Box 26, Folder 220)
      - Action (Box 26, Folder 220)
    - Gymnastics
      - 1869 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - circa 1874 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - 1875 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - 1892 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - circa 1896 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - 1901 (Box 30, Folder 254)
      - Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 254)
    - Hockey [see also oversize]
      - 1895 (Box 25, Folder 211)
      - 1900-1901 (Box 25, Folder 211)
      - 1906-1910 (Box 25, Folder 211)
      - 1911 (Box 25, Folder 212)
      - 1913-1916 (Box 25, Folder 212)
      - 1920, individual portraits (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1927, freshman (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1928, freshman (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1931 (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1932 (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 25, Folder 213)
      - 1933 (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1934 (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1935-circa 1935 (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1942 (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1944, action (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1944, freshman (Box 25, Folder 214)
      - 1952 (Box 25, Folder 215)
      - circa 1965 (Box 25, Folder 215)
      - 1967, action (Box 25, Folder 215)
      - 1968 (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - 1970 (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - circa 1970 (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - 1971, freshman (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - 1977, action (Women) (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - 2000, action (Box 25, Folder 216)
      - Unidentified (Box 25, Folder 216)
    - Lacrosse
      - 1918 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1926 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1931 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1932 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1933 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1934 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1937, action (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - circa 1962 (Box 30, Folder 249)
      - Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 249)
    - Polo [see also oversize]
      - 1923-1927 (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1930-1932 (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1934 (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1935 (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1935, freshman (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1936, freshman (Box 26, Folder 221)
      - 1937, action (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1939, action (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1940 (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1941, 1943, and 1945, freshman (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1953 (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1954, action (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1962 (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1965, action (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - 1967, action (Box 26, Folder 222)
      - Unidentified (Box 26, Folder 223)
      - Team Portraits (Box 26, Folder 223)
      - Action (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - Rifle and Gun [see also oversize]
      - 1905, 1910, 1915, 1921 (Box 31, Folder 263)
      - Unidentified: Captain (Box 31, Folder 263)
    - Rock Climbing
      - 1971 (Box 31, Folder 261)
    - Rugby [see also oversize]
      - Action: 1876, 1884, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1938, 1940, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 258)
    - Sailing
      - 1894, 1902, 1903, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 259)
    - Scuba
      - 1971 (Box 31, Folder 262)
    - Skiing
      - 1971 (Box 31, Folder 260)
      - Unidentified (Box 31, Folder 260)
    - Soccer
      - 1923, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1932, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1934 (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - 1941 (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - Action 2000 (Box 31, Folder 265)
      - Unidentified (Box 31, Folder 265)
    - Squash
      - 1932, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 266)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 31, Folder 266)
      - 1953, action (Box 31, Folder 266)
      - circa 1964 (Box 31, Folder 266)
      - 1970, action (Box 31, Folder 266)
      - Unidentified:, action (Box 31, Folder 266)
    - Swimming
      - Swimming Association, intercollegiate champions, 1904 (Box 38)
      - Swimming team, 1913 (Box 38)
      - Swimming team, 1914 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, 1914 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, 1915 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, intercollegiate champions, 1916 (Box 38)
      - World champion relay team (200 yards), 1917 March 21 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, intercollegiate champions, 1917 (Box 38)
      - Richard Mayer, captain of swim team, 1918 (Box 38)
      - Eugene Peterson, member of swim team and water polo team, 1918 (Box 38)
      - Championship swim team, 1919 (Box 38)
      - World record 200 yard relay team, 1919 March 14 (Box 38)
      - University swimming team, 1920 (Box 38)
      - Yale 200 yard relay team, 1920 (Box 38)
      - Freshmen, 1933 (Box 38)
      - Varsity, 1934 (Box 38)
      - Stroke analysis/biomechanical studies, circa 1940s (Box 39)
      - Eastern Intercollegiate Swimming League champs, 1949 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, 1949 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, 1952 (Box 38)
      - Varsity swim team, 1953 (Box 38)
      - Freshmman swim team, 1953 (Box 38)
      - Varsity swim team, 1954 (Box 38)
      - Varsity swim team, 1957 (Box 38)
      - Varsity swim team, 1958 (Box 38)
      - AAU championships, 1958 (Box 38)
      - Swim team, 1959 (Box 38)
      - American swim team at 1964 Olympics, Tokyo, Japan. Includes 5 Yalies: Schollander, Clark, Townsend, Netter (Box 38)
      - John Nelson and team beating Stanford, 1969 (Box 38)
      - Phil Moriarity retirement party, 1976 (Box 38)
    - Tennis
      - 1911, action (Box 19, Folder 165)
      - 1921 (Box 19, Folder 165)
      - 1924 (Box 19, Folder 165)
      - 1924, freshman (Box 19, Folder 166)
      - 1933? (Box 19, Folder 166)
      - 1934 Wright (Intramural?) (Box 19, Folder 166)
      - 1937 (Practice) Snapshots (Box 19, Folder 167)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 19, Folder 167)
      - 1952 (Box 19, Folder 167)
      - 1961 Yale-Princeton, action (Box 19, Folder 168)
      - 1967, action (Box 19, Folder 168)
      - Unidentified: (Box 19, Folder 169)
      - Team Portraits (Box 19, Folder 169)
      - Action (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Track [see also oversize and folio]
      - 1887-1891 (Box 26, Folder 224)
      - 1892 (Box 26, Folder 225)
      - 1893 (Box 26, Folder 225)
      - 1894 (Box 26, Folder 226)
      - 1895 (Box 26, Folder 226)
      - 1896-1897 (Box 26, Folder 227)
      - 1897, action (Hurdles) (Box 26, Folder 227)
      - 1898-1901 (Box 26, Folder 227)
      - 1902 (Box 27, Folder 228)
      - 1903 (Box 27, Folder 229)
      - 1903, individual portraits (Box 27, Folder 229)
      - 1903 Non-Yale, individual portraits (Box 27, Folder 229)
      - 1904-1906 (Box 27, Folder 230)
      - 1907-1910 (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1910, action (Pole Vault) (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1910, freshman (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1911 (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1911, action (Footrace) (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1911, freshman (Box 27, Folder 231)
      - 1912 (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - 1912, freshman (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - 1913 (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - 1913, freshman (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - 1914 (Box 27, Folder 232)
      - 1915 (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1915, freshman (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1916 (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1916, freshman (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1917-1918 (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1918, freshman (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1919 (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1919, freshman (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - 1920-1921 (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1921, freshman (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1923, freshman (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1924 (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1924, freshman (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1925 (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1925, freshman (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1926 (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1926, freshman (Box 28, Folder 234)
      - 1927 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1927, freshman (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1928 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1928, freshman (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1929 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1929 Mile Relay Team (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1930 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1930 Mile Relay Team (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - circa 1930 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1931 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1931 Mile Relay Team (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1932 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - circa 1932 (Box 28, Folder 235)
      - 1933 (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1934 (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1935 (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1935, freshman (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1935, action, Intercollegiate, (100m, 20 lb. Hammer) (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1936 (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1936, freshman (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1936, action (Long jump) (Box 28, Folder 236)
      - 1937 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1937, freshman (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1937, action (Indoor footrace) (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1938 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1938, action (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1939 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1940 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1940, freshman (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1941 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1941, freshman (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1942 (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1942, action (Hurdles) (Box 28, Folder 237)
      - 1946-1948 (Box 28, Folder 238)
      - 1949freshman (Box 28, Folder 238)
      - 1950-1954 (Box 28, Folder 238)
      - 1955-1965 (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1957, action (Running, Relay) (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1958 (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1958, freshman (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1961 (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1961, action (Long Jump, Javelin) (Box 29, Folder 239)
      - 1962-1965 (Box 29, Folder 240)
      - 1967, action (Running, Long Jump) (Box 29, Folder 240)
      - 1968, action (Box 29, Folder 240)
      - circa 1968 (Box 29, Folder 240)
      - Unidentified (Box 29, Folder 240)
      - Unidentified (Box 29, Folder 241)
      - Action (Hurdles, Running, Relay, Pole Vault, Hammer, Shotput) (Box 29, Folder 241)
      - 1904-1906 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - 1913 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - circa 1914 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - 1915 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - 1918-1920 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 29, Folder 242)
      - 1924 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1924, freshman (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1925-1926 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - circa 1928 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - circa 1929 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1931, freshman (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1932 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1932, freshman (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1933 (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 29, Folder 243)
      - 1934 (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1935 (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1935, freshman (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1935, action (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1937, action (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1938, action (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1939 (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1941, individual portraits (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1942, action (Box 29, Folder 244)
      - 1945,, action (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1946, action (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1949 (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1953 Trophy (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1954 (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1957 Trophy (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1961, action (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - circa 1964 (Box 29, Folder 245)
      - 1970, freshman (Box 29, Folder 246)
      - Action (Box 29, Folder 246)
      - Individual Portraits (Box 29, Folder 246)
      - circa 1977, action (women) (Box 29, Folder 246)
      - Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 247)
      - Team Portraits (Box 30, Folder 247)
      - Action (Box 30, Folder 247)
      - Individual Portraits (Box 30, Folder 247)
    - Volleyball
      - circa 1977, action (women) (Box 31, Folder 268)
    - Water Polo
      - 1890s, 1904 (Box 31, Folder 267)
      - 1907 (Box 38)
      - 1913, 1918-1921, 1923-1926, 1931-1933 (Box 31, Folder 267)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 31, Folder 267)
      - 1935 (Box 31, Folder 267)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 31, Folder 267)
    - Wrestling
      - 1905, 1915, 1918, 1929, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1933, freshman (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1934, freshman (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1935 (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1938, freshman (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1942, action (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1949 (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - 1969 (Box 30, Folder 248)
      - Unidentified (Box 30, Folder 248)
  - Oversize
    - Athletic Association, 1931, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Baseball
      - 1875, 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, circa 1889 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - circa 1888 with Alfonso Stagg (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Field and Team Photos (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 1904 (Law School), 1918, 1919-1921 (Graduate School and Seminary League), circa 1925, circa 1930, 1933, circa 1950 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - no date (Box 32, Folder 6-7)
    - Cheerleaders (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Crew
      - 1861, 1887, 1892, 1894, 1896 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - George Langford (1897) Album of Crew; Trip to Henley Regatta in England (Box 33, Folder 10-11)
      - no date (1890's) (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - 1902, 1906 (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
      - 1907, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - 1909, 1910 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Varsity Team with B. F. Tolles, circa 1890s (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Football
      - 1878, 1880, 1881, 1883, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1894, 1899, no date (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Drawing, 1891, 1911 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Captains, unidentified, 1914, 1915 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - 1900-1901, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - 1905, 1906, 1907, 1910, 1911, 1933-1939 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Walter Camp, 1940 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Teams, 1941 October 4 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Alex Wilson, 1941 October 11 (Box 35, Folder 25)
      - Program Covers, 1941 October 18 (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - Drawings from Football Through the Years, 1941 October 25 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Yale-Virginia Program, 1941 November 15 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Yale-Penn Program (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Yale-Army Program (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Yale-Dartmouth Programs, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Yale-Princeton Program, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Teams, undated (Box 36, Folder 33-36)
    - Hockey
      - 1876, 1904, 1919, 1920, 1934 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - 1932, 1911 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Team (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - Freshman Teams, 1907 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Captains (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - Polo (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - Riflery (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - Rugby, circa 1923 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - Soccer, freshman Team (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - Swimming (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - Track
      - Team photographs, 1892, 1893, 1910; Program Cover (Yale vs. Harvard), 1907 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Mike Murphy- Coach (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Water Polo
      - 1904, circa 1910, circa 1915 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - All Sports
      - 1899, 1910, no date (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Group Photographs of Athletic Teams Belonging to Thomas Campbell (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Folio
    - Baseball
      - 1913 (Folder DR16F54)
      - Yale vs. Harvard, 1914 (Folder DR16F54)
      - 1918 (Folder DR16F54)
      - Game (Folder DR16F54)
      - Yale team (Folder DR16F54)
      - Unidentified (Folder DR16F54)
    - Boxing
      - Newspaper Photos, circa 1923 (Folder DR17F55)
      - Exercise, undated (Folder DR17F55)
    - Crew
      - Drawings and articles in Harper's, 1865-1889 (Folder DR15F51)
      - Color Print of race by J.M. Barnsby, 1890 (Folder DR15F51)
      - Drawings and articles in New York Herald (Folder DR15F51)
      - Harpers, 1890, 1891-1893 (Folder DR15F51)
      - 1904 (Folder DR15F51)
      - Yale vs. Harvard, 1904, 1910 (Folder DR15F51)
      - 1905 (Folder DR15F51)
      - 1906 (Folder 271)
      - at Gale's ferry, circa 1917 (Folder DR15F51)
      - circa 1920s (Folder 271)
      - circa 1917, 1926, 1929, 1933 (Folder 271)
    - Football
      - Color Print of Yale-Princeton game, 1876 (Folder DR16F52)
      - Illustration's in Harper's, 1887-1893 (Folder DR16F52)
      - 1887 (Folder DR16F52)
      - 1900 (Folder DR16F52)
      - 1901 (Folder DR16F52)
      - Yale vs Harvard in New Haven, 1902, 1904, 1906 (Folder DR16F52)
      - Game, 1905 (Folder DR16F52)
      - Practice, 1907 (Folder DR16F52)
      - Team, 1908 (Folder 272)
      - 1909 (Folder DR16F52)
      - 1910 (Folder DR16F53)
      - Dinner, 1911 (Folder DR16F53)
      - Construction of Yale Bowl, 1913-1914 (Folder 272)
      - Yale vs. Harvard-1st game played in Yale Bowl, 1914 (Folder DR16F53)
      - Yale vs. Princeton, 1915 (Folder 272, Folder DR16F53)
      - Yale vs. Harvard, 1916 (Folder DR16F53)
      - Yale vs. Princeton at Yale Bowl, 1921 (Folder DR16F53)
      - 1922 (Folder DR16F53)
      - West Point cadets at Yale Bowl, 1923 (Folder 272)
      - Yale vs. Harvard? (Folder DR16F53)
      - Unidentified (Folder DR16F53)
      - Team, 1976 (Folder 272)
      - Yale-Harvard game, 1978 (Folder 272)
      - Yale vs. Harvard, 2007 November 17 (Folder 270)
    - Posters with Handsome Dan
      - Till life's sun is set we will never forget (Folder DR15F50)
      - Well Rowed Yale by A.B. Graves (2 copies) (Folder DR15F50)
      - Hold 'em Yale by A.B. Graves (3 copies) (Folder DR15F50)
    - Track
      - Championship team, 1903 (Folder DR17F56)
      - Yale-Harvard race, undated (Folder DR17F56)
    - All Sports
      - Athletic Calendar, 1893 (Folder DR17F57)
- Original illustration and printers proofs for official souvenir football programs, circa 1933-1941; Accession 19ND-A-458
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Brown, 1933 October 21 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Army, 1935 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dartmouth, 1935 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brown, 1935 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Princeton, 1935 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Navy, 1935 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Princeton, 1935 November 30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1941 October 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Penn, 1941 October 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Army, 1941 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dartmouth, 1941 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Brown, 1941 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Princeton, 1941 November 15 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Printer's proofs, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Penn, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dartmouth, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Penn, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Harvard, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cornell, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Army, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Photographs of various athletic teams, circa 1908-1934; Accession 19ND-A-459
  - Yale football team (unidentified), 1933 (Box 1)
  - Vanderbilt football team, 1934 (Box 1)
  - Yale football team, 1910 (Box 1)
  - Yale football coaching staff, circa 1921 (Box 1)
  - Yale football coaching staff, undated (Box 1)
  - "Bullshit Eleven", circa 1908 (Box 1)
  - Yale athletic captains, undated (Box 1)
  - Athletic Association banquet?, undated (Box 1)
- Photographic negatives (glass) of Yale athletic events, circa 1900s; Accession 1992-A-075 (Box 1–4)
  Access is restricted.
  No online inventory available.
- Photographs of intramural sports, circa 1930-1960; Accession 2005-A-056
  Arranged alphabetically by sport.
  - Baseball, 1934-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Basketball, 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Crew, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fencing, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football, 1934-1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football, 1939-1955, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football, undated (Box 1, Folder 7 - 12)
  - Golf, 1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hockey, 1934, 1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Squash, 1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Swimming, 1938, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Tennis, 1938, 1946, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Track, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wrestling, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)